

Product & Web Designer

I am a product and web designer with 10+ years of experience. I worked in teams on high-impact, large projects for brands like Ford, Telekom, Graphisoft, and Samsung. I helped my former company win 3 creative awards (and support wildlife) with a sustainable website.

Budapest, Hungary +36 20 617 6328 gergo.zambo.designer@gmail.com gergozambo.com

linkedin.com/in/gergozambo

Experience

Product (ux/ui) Designer Ergomania (2023-present)

- Leading cross-platform mobile app design projects for British fintech startups to help them focus on user needs and go to market
- · Redesigning images and identities of international brands
- · Conducting competitor analysis, interviews, and user research
- Managing the internal AI research and design team to innovate and improve design workflows

VML (2019-2023)

Senior Digital (ux/u1) Designer

- · Led copywriters and designers to develop creative concepts
- · Developed and utilized design systems of global brands
- · Designed mobile apps and games for digital promotions
- Won 3 creative awards for designing a sustainable website that helped raise awareness of water pollution

Digital (ux/u1) Designer

- Took part in day-long branding workshops for startups and global companies, helping them create their brand's core ideas
- Redesigned a global tech company's brand image and website, positioned it as a market leader

Graphic & Web Designer Tricky (2017-2019)

 Designed user flows, UI kits, and developer handoffs for music streaming platforms, generated lots of uploads and high traffic

Graphic & Web Designer Freelance (2016-2017)

- · Led redesign and design projects for corporate & state organizations
- Conducted thorough UX audit and research of large webshops

Art Director & Editor-in-Chief ELTE (2014-2016)
Junior Front-End Developer Mito (2013)
Web Design Intern Everengine (2012)

Tools

- · Figma, FigJam, Miro
- · Notion, ClickUp, Slack
- · Adobe Ps, Ai, Id, Acrobat
- · Midjourney, ChatGPT

Skills

- · Wireframing, prototyping
- uı design
- · Design systems
- · Brand identity design
- Typography
- User testing
- Interviews, workshops
- Competitor analysis
- ux & website audits
- Accessibility
- HTML, CSS, SEO
- Generative AI
- Project, task & stakeholder management

Education, training

Product (UX/UI) Designer MOME (2020)

Design Theory MA MOME (2017-2019)

Linguistics & Literature BA ELTE (2013-2016)

Languages

- English (C1, Full professional proficiency)
- · Hungarian (Native)

For more about my experiences, awards, and projects, please see my LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/gergozambo

